<string><COLOR FF0000>#Rejected#</COLOR> QD_QN030101
<string><CAM:0>Yo, Ace! What's up!?<lf>Accepted my quest, huh? Niiiiice!
<string>Come over here and we'll get started!
<string><CAM:23>Congrats again on making hunter!<lf>A whole new life awaits!
<string>Heh! I can see it in your eyes that you're<lf>ready to thrash, but let's do a little<lf>quest refresher first, cool?
<string>Let's start with our <COLS RED>Camp</COL> here.
<string><CAM:1>This is your <COLS RED>Tent</COL>. Here, you can<lf>change your equipment and<lf>weapons, or organize your items.
<string>If you wanna bail on your current<lf>loadout, you're free to switch<lf>out your gear inside.
<string><CAM:2>That over there is the <COLS RED>Supply Box</COL>.<lf>It's full of useful items that'll aid<lf>you during a quest.
<string>And everything in there is provided<lf>by the Guild so feel free to take<lf>and use whatever you want!
<string>...And that's it for the Camp.<lf>Let's move on to the next part!
<string><CAM:15,16,17>I'll meet you down by the river past<lf>the ledge. If you get lost, just look<lf>for my icon on your map!
<string><CAM:4>Heeey! Up here!
<string>Alright, let's talk <COLS RED>Wirebugs</COL>!<lf>These bodacious bugs are<lf>a must in any hunt!
<string>Use 'em right, and you'll be able to zip<lf>around to pretty much anywhere you<lf>wanna go! Even on top of this boulder!
<string>Give it a shot!
<string><CAM:24>Hey! Look at that!<lf>You're a natural!
<string>Next, let's talk <COLS RED>Buddies</COL>!
<string><CAM:11><OTTUTO>Today, I brought my <COLS RED>Palico</COL> and<lf><COL RED>Palamute</COL>, Flash and Rumble,<lf>with me.
<string>They'll be lendin' you a paw for<lf>this part of the training.
<string>First, try <COLS RED>mounting</COL> Rumble, my Palamute!
<string>Palamutes are swift as the wind,<lf>so if a monster gives you the slip,<lf>hop on your barking Buddy!
<string><CAM:7,8,9>Alright, I'll be waiting for you<lf>up the trail. Meet me there!
<string><CAM:24>You alright, Ace?<lf>Wirebugs giving you trouble?
<string>If you're struggling, hold <OPT ZL> while<lf>aiming with <ICON ANALOG_RS> and once your reticle<lf>is pointing at the right spot, press <OPT ZR>!
<string>Don't sweat it, yo! You'll be a master of<lf>Wirebugs in no time if you just keep practicing!
<string>Next, let's talk <COLS RED>Buddies</COL>!
<string><CAM:11><OTTUTO>Today, I brought my <COLS RED>Palico</COL> and<lf><COL RED>Palamute</COL>, Flash and Rumble,<lf>with me.
<string>They'll be lendin' you a paw for<lf>this part of the training.
<string>First, try <COLS RED>mounting</COL> Rumble, my Palamute!
<string>Palamutes are swift as the wind,<lf>so if a monster gives you the slip,<lf>hop on your barking Buddy!
<string><CAM:7,8,9>Alright, I'll be waiting for you<lf>up the trail. Meet me there!
<string><CAM:5>Hey! Check out this <COLS RED>Yellow Spiribird</COL>.
<string>If you touch one, its pollen will<lf>enhance that good-luck charm<lf>you're wearing—your <COLS RED>Petalace</COL>.
<string>When that happens, the scent of<lf>the pollen surrounds your Petalace<lf>and boosts your stats.
<string>Since this li'l guy is yellow,<lf>it'll increase your stamina.
<string>Similarly, Spiribirds of other colors<lf>will boost other stats. Pretty gnarly,<lf>if you ask me!
<string>The effect is only active during the current<lf>quest, but you can be sure as shurikens<lf>that they are worth using!
<string><CAM:6>Oh, and that's a <COLS RED>Clothfly</COL> over there!
<string>Clothflies are one of many creatures<lf>you'll come across out in the field!<lf>We call these li'l guys Endemic Life.
<string>The powder these floaty friends<lf>spread can boost your defense!
<string>There's lots of other Endemic Life<lf>out there that can boost your hunts<lf>in different ways!
<string><CAM:5>Have a look around for other Endemic<lf>Life, and then play around with them<lf>to see what kinds of effects they have!
<string>OK, just a li'l bit more!<lf>Follow me.
<string><CAM:12>Right on, Ace!<lf>Got the hang of riding Palamutes already?
<string>They're super helpful Buddies,<lf>especially when you need to<lf>cover a lot of ground!
<string>And you can even tell them to<lf>attack while you're riding 'em!
<string>But their attacks won't be as<lf>strong as yours...
<string>So when you're ready to get down<lf>to business, it's best to dismount.
<string><CAM:13>Oh! Looks like we got ourselves<lf>some monsters nearby.
<string><CAM:12>How are your health and stamina<lf>looking? Be sure to keep tabs on<lf>your status while out in the field.
<string>When you're ready, let's head up<lf>this way; it's time to really get<lf>this show on the road!
<string><CAM:12>Decided to travel on foot this time?<lf>Well, just remember: All you gotta do is<lf>hold <ICON PAD_A> next to a Palamute to ride it.
<string>And you can even tell them to<lf>attack while you're riding 'em!
<string>But their attacks won't be as<lf>strong as yours...
<string>So when you're ready to get down<lf>to business, it's best to dismount.
<string><CAM:13>Oh! Looks like we got ourselves<lf>some monsters nearby.
<string><CAM:12>How are your health and stamina<lf>looking? Be sure to keep tabs on<lf>your status while out in the field.
<string>When you're ready, let's head up<lf>this way; it's time to really get<lf>this show on the road!
<string><CAM:42,43,10><EMTUTO_DISP>Gnarly! A pack of Izuchi.<lf>Alright, there's three of 'em.<lf>Go take 'em out for me!
<string>Don't hold back just because<lf>they're small now! They can<lf>be skillful and ruthless!
<string>Just remember your training<lf>and you'll be golden!
<string><EMTUTO_THINK>Now, ready your weapon, nice<lf>and steady, and take 'em down<lf>one attack at a time.
<string>What's up, Ace? You should be over thrashin'<lf>those Izuchi!
<string><CAM:14>Sweet! Awesome job there, Ace!
<string>Oh, and don't forget to <COLS RED>carve</COL> to harvest<lf>materials from monsters. They can be<lf>used for upgrades at the Smithy!
<string>When you're done carving, come see me!
<string>Just as I expected from my star pupil!<lf>That was an incredible hunt.
<string>If there's something you think you<lf>could've done better, don't worry!<lf>After all, you're just getting started.
<string>Now then, let's head back to camp.<lf>And it looks like we're kinda far<lf>away from it...
<string>But no big deal, yo! Use <COLS RED>Fast Travel</COL><lf>and you'll be back at camp in no time.
<string>I'm gonna go ahead. See you there!
<string>Congratulations!<lf>You've completed this basic training quest!
<string>I'm now proud to send you<lf>out into the field as a full-<lf>fledged hunter!
<string>You've learned well.<lf>But keep in mind: Elder Fugen<lf>and I expect much from you!
<string>
<string>I'd be happy to guide you through<lf>it again!
<string><CAM:19>Hey there, Ace! Came here to learn<lf>about <COLS RED>Wyvern Riding</COL>, huh? Awesome!
<string>Well I'm happy to show you how!<lf>OK, let's start off with the basics!
<string>Wyvern Riding is a gnarly technique<lf>that uses <COLS RED>Ironsilk</COL> to bend a monster<lf>to your will!
<string>While Wyvern Riding, you can force the<lf>monster to attack other monsters, or even<lf>slam it into walls, dealing massive damage!
<string>Now, there are a few steps you gotta take<lf>to successfully hang ten on a monster!
<string>And that's what we'll be practicing today!
<string>So, once you're good to go, head on down!<lf>I'll give you more info once you do.
<string>You ready to ride, Ace!?<lf>Here's the rundown:
<string>First, in order to Wyvern Ride, you'll need<lf>to get a monster into a <COLS RED>Mountable State</COL>.
<string>There are lots of ways to accomplish<lf>this, but first, let's give the ol' Wirebug<lf><COLS RED>Silkbind</COL> method a shot!
<string>If you keep attacking a monster using<lf>Silkbind attacks, it'll eventually get all<lf>tangled up and become mountable.
<string>Since you'll be using a Wirebug for this,<lf>it'll consume your <COL RED>Wirebug Gauge</COL>. Just<lf>like Wiredashing, mind your gauge!
<string>Silkbind works differently with each<lf>weapon type, so try 'em all out!
<string>You wanna take a sec to practice?<lf>Let me know when you've had your fill!
<string><CAM:21>You all clear on how to use<lf>the Silkbind technique?
<string>Alright then! Next up, it's time to practice<lf>using a most excellent Endemic Lifeform,<lf>the <COL RED>Puppet Spider</COL>!
<string><CAM:22>There's a Puppet Spider right over there!
<string>In skillful hands, the sticky, sturdy, silky<lf>strands that this spider produces can be<lf>used to make a monster mountable.
<string><CAM:21>When it comes to mounting monsters,<lf>you can use the Silkbind technique or<lf>a Puppet Spider—either works!
<string>Approach a Mountable monster and<lf>attack it or press <ICON PAD_A> with your weapon<lf>sheathed to start Wyvern Riding!
<string>So, are ya clear on how to start Wyvern Riding?<lf>Cool. Now all that's left is to try out for real<lf>and see what method fits yours style!
<string>Ready to give it a shot? Good!<lf>I've prepared an Arzuros just for<lf>the occasion!
<string>Both methods work, so just focus on<lf>getting it into a Mountable State first!
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
<string>
